Krzysztof Maciejczuk

maciejczuk.krzysztof@gmail.com 796 157 493

https://github.com/EricFelixLuther/



IT Tools

Python

- o Django
- CherryPy

JavaScript

- jQuery
- Angular

Databases

- MySQL
- PostgreSQL
- SQLite

Operating Systems

- Ubuntu
- Fedora
- Windows

CSS

Bootstrap

С

Java

Selenium

IT Skills

SCRUM Methodology

JIRA System

App design

I am a Python programmer with three years of experience, and also I am a game enthusiast (love games). My dream is to join work career with my passion for games. For this position I have following skills: good Python knowledge, great english skills (finished studies), positive attitude, good knowledge of JavaScript, ridiculously redundant knowledge about games.

Work Experience

2015.03 until now

Samsung Electronics Polska - Junior Software Engineer Responsibilities:

Work on a long term project - intranet corporate system

Web app maintenance and development

SQL database handling

Writing JavaScript and jQuery

Writing documentation (UML enthusiast)

Front-end (HTML, CSS)

Automation test design

Linux server maintenance

Achievements:

Enhancing code quality and optimising its execution time.

Implementing new, bug-free functionalities according to client's expectations.

2012.11 - Samsung Electronics Polska - Software Tester Responsibilities:

Exploratory tests

User interface tests

Verification through test cases

Bug reports and cooperation with developers

Planning, designing and writing automated test scripts

Achievements:

Keeping high bug report scores

Found many issues with high priority

Education

2012 - 2017	European University in Warsaw, specialization: Mobile and Webapps Inżynier
2006 - 2011	SWPS University of Social Sciences and Humanities, English Philology Bachelor degree
2003 - 2006	13'th Highschool in Warsaw, Math-Computer sciences profiled class Matura

Interests & Hobbys
Electronics (Arduino, Raspberry Pi)
Mobile apps
Virtual Reality
Latest technologies
Video / board games
Apps and games design
Fantasy (steampunk, dieselpunk)
Swing dance

Foreign Languages				
English	C1			
German	B1			
Spanish	A1			

Other work experience			
Booking.com 2011 - 2012 Booking Button Specialist			
Empik 2010 - 2011 Photo lab, customer service			
American Bookstore 2008 - 2010 online shop			
Barman 2007, 2008 Spain			

Trainings			
Time	Course name	Organizer	Certified
October 2017	Bootstrap 4	Udemy	Yes
September 2017	Angular	Udemy	Yes
December 2016	Clean Code	Samsung Electronics	No
April 2015	Algorithms	Samsung Electronics	No
January 2016	Selenium: introduction	Samsung Electronics	No
September 2014	Python, advanced	Samsung Electronics	No
June-July 2014	App Design Course	Adobe Generation	Yes
May-June 2014	Games Design Course	Adobe Generation	Yes
January-June 2014	Introduction to Computer Science and Programming	edX.org & MITx	Yes

I hereby give consent for my personal data included in my application to be processed for the purposes of the recruitment process under the Personal Data Protection Act as of 29 August 1997, consolidated text: Journal of Laws 2016, item 922 as amended.